boostime.in 2018-01-17

# Privacy policy

Boostime strives to protect its users' privacy complying with law.  
The collection and processing of personal data has been notified (receipt #) to the french National Commission for Data protection and the Liberties (CNIL).  
This document informs you on how you personal data are collected and processed when you use our website and services.  
Boostime is committed to update this page whenever any change occurs in our policy or in your rights. 

**Personal data**  
By accessing our website, you acknowledge and agree that your personal data will be collected, transfered, stored and processed by Boostime on our servers (located in the European Union).  
You also agree to receive commercial communications from us, unless you mentioned you do not wish to receive such communications.  
Boostime will NOT sell, rent nor share your personal data to any third party, with the exception of requests by law enforcement authorities to disclose information about users posting any illegal material. 

**What kind of personal data do we collect?**  
By placing an ad on Boostime, you are deemed to have accepted that your ad details get accessible online by the public. As our servers are located in the European Union, you accept that your personal data will be transfered and stored on our servers in Europe. We collect and store the following data:

  * e-mail address, post code, city (or country, if overseas), ad title and description. Additional information can be required, depending on the type of ad posted, (eg ads for personals: age, sex, hobbies, ...);

  * data and statistics related to connection, traffic and browsing on Boostime.

**Purpose of collection and processing of personal data**  
We use your personal data :

  * to run the ad posting service;  

  * to improve and optimize the contents and services we propose;
  * to assess user interest in the website;
  * to inform users about new services and offers.

**Use of user data posted on Boostime  
**The personal data featured on Boostime are to be used ONLY to contact a user about a specific ad, and by no means to send unsolicited commercial communications, nor to collect the user's contact details whithout his/her prior consent.

**Your rights**  
Pursuant to the French Act n° 78-17 of 6 January 1978 on Data Processes, Data Files and Individual Liberties, you are entitled to access, modify, rectify and delete any personal data (art. 34 of the Act), as collected and processed by Boostime.  
**The website enables you to view, modify or delete** the personally-identifying information such as your ads, login details (email, password), profile (post code, city, country, status) via "My ads & messages" accessible from the Boostime home page with the email address and password that you chose when you placed your first ad.
